# Gino Ghalehpardaz

519-852-9960 • ginoghalehpardaz@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/gino-ghalehpardaz-7b4a05122 • www.ginoghal.ca

## Front-End Developer, Motion Designer, Multimedia & Marketing Specialist

Ambitious, results-driven interactive media professional with expertise in front-end website development, graphic and motion design, marketing, content development, and social media management. Intuitively adapt to new technology and innovative processes while ensuring compliance with corporate and client standards. *Areas of Emphasis Include...* 

- Adobe Creative Suite: Photoshop, Illustrator, Premiere, Audition, Acrobat, After Effects & InDesign
- Bilingual Proficient in French, Farsi
- WordPress & GitHub
- Social Media, Hootsuite & Mailchimp
- Web Development, U/X & U/I
- HTML, CSS, SASS, & JavaScript
- Motion & 3-D Design
- Google Analytics and SEO
- Creative & Artistic Direction
- Animation & Video Production

### **EDUCATION**

Interactive Media Design Diploma | Fanshawe College, London, Ontario (2020)

Bachelor's Degree with Honours in Journalism & Criminology | Wilfrid Laurier University, Branford, Ontario (2014)

### **EXPERIENCE HIGHLIGHTS**

Media Specialist & Driver, BIJAN'S ART STUDIO, London, ON, 9/2009 to Present

Market Bijan's Art Studio by developing and implementing promotional advertising campaigns. Manage the online presence, website copy, and digital communications through the Customer Management System (CMS). Conduct sales research to analyze customer behavior, purchasing habits, trends, and preferences.

- Promoted from a store customer service representative due to providing exceptional assistance. Additionally, serve
  as the floor manager in the store owner's absence.
- Instrumental in increasing retail transactions by designing eye-catching advertisements to promote sale items.

Marketing Coordinator, QUADRO COMMUNICATIONS CO-OPERATIVE, INC., Kirkton, ON, 3/2017 to 9/2018

Directed the social media, website, and digital marketing strategy in collaboration with managers to increase brand awareness. Oversaw the newsletter content development process by writing articles that highlighted company news, selecting appropriate images, editing copy, crafting appealing layouts, delivering emails to distribution lists, and analyzing circulation statistics. Conducted robust industry research on the competitive landscape to position the company as a market leader. Reviewed website analytics such as Click-Through Rates (CTR), traffic, audience engagement and behavior, bounce rates, and acquisition sources to provide management with insights and recommendations for improving website optimization performance.

Increased total followers and user interactions on social media pages by creating engaging, interactive content.

#### **INTERNSHIPS**

Web Developer & Design Intern, ILDERTON AREA BUSINESS ASSOCIATION (IABA), Ilderton, ON, 4/2020 to 6/2020

Selected by the IABA to redesign the association's website and digital blueprint in the WordPress platform. Utilized U/X and U/I best practices to generate engaging mockup wireframes and developed/updated the new website to meet the IABA's requirements by adding features including a business map API, business association, clean images and functionality and more.

Social Media Management Intern, BTC FIGHT PROMOTIONS, Burlington, ON, 1/2020 to 5/2020

Oversaw the BTC Fight Instagram and Facebook social media channels. Produced promotional videos and images to promote MMA events. Increased followers by more than 1000 subscribers, achieved 450 views on the video, and improved overall engagement by consistently developing captivating posts and interacting with fans.